(upbeat music)
When customers shop in the Amazon store,
they are able to see all seller offers
on a single product detail page.
This page also shows all product versions or variations,
for example sizes or colors.
This helps customers find the products they want
and compare offers more easily.
It also saves you the seller from having to recreate pages
for products that already exist in the Amazon catalog.
Sellers approved to sell a product
are able to suggest edits to its product detail page
with some exceptions.
This is different than changing your offer for a product,
which you can do at any time for any products you sell.
To suggest an edit to a product detail page,
start by opening the seller central main menu,
hover over inventory and select manage all inventory.
On the manage all inventory page,
find the product you'd like to suggest an edit for.
At the end of the row,
click on the three dots and select edit listing.
This will take you to the offer tab
where you can edit your offer for a product.
The offer tab is where you can edit price, sales
and item condition.
You may also be able to edit options
for features like gifting.
As mentioned earlier,
you can make changes to your offer for all products you sell
and updated information will typically appear
in the Amazon store within 15 minutes.
If you have permission to suggest edits
to the product detail page,
you'll see multiple tabs alongside the offer tab
at the top of the screen.
These tabs include product details, images,
variations and safety and compliance.
The product details tab includes essential information
about a product like item name, brand name,
product description and keywords.
Note that you may not be able to suggest an edit
for all fields.
In the images tab, you will be able to see
all the images currently live on the product detail page.
You may also be able to upload your recommendation
for product images.
If the product is available in different versions
for color, size, style or other attributes,
you can use the variations page for the parent product
to add or edit a variation type.
If you want to edit other information
specific to a variation,
click edit at the end of the row
to access the offer and product pages for that variation.
In the safety and compliance tab,
you will see fields related to product safety,
for example, battery information.
After you've made your suggested edit,
click the save and finish button
at the bottom of the page.
When multiple sellers sell the same product
through a single detail page,
we combine and present the best product data
to ensure customers get the best experience.
If your suggestion is selected,
it will usually appear on the product detail page
within 24 hours.